ILGWU. Gus Tyler papers, 5780/052
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VI. Subject files., 1950-1975
  - Twentieth Century Fund, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    Incl. conference on reapportionment of state legislatures, June 1962.
  - Tyler, Gus [folder 1 of 2], 1963 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    Corres. and newspaper clippings on Tyler's appointment as Assistant President.
  - Tyler, Gus [folder 2 of 2], 1963 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Television and Radios, 1960-1963 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - U, 1970-1973 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - United Farm Workers Organizing Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    Incl. corres re fundraising, boycott.
  - Union Label Department, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Union Label Department [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Union Label Department [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Union Label Department, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - United Federation of Teachers, N.Y.C., Strikes [folder 1 of 3], 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - United Federation of Teachers, N.Y.C., Strikes [folder 2 of 3], 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - United Federation of Teachers, N.Y.C., Strikes [folder 3 of 3], 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - University of Scranton Alumni Association, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Upper South Department [folder 1 of 3], 1963-1973 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Upper South Department [folder 2 of 3], 1963-1973 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Upper South Department [folder 3 of 3], 1963-1973 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Vietnam, 1962-1973 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Visitors, 1969-1972 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Corres. re visits to Union, briefings of Foreign Service Officers on the Union.
  - Voter Registration, 1962-1963 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Voter Registration, 1968-1973 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Incl. Corres. w. Victor Gotbaum, Morris Iushewitz, Morris Abram, Jr., and Andrew Stein.
  - W, 1961-1973 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Weatherhead Foundation [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1974 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Weatherhead Foundation [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1974 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Western States Region, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Which Way for Labor in Politics, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Tyler article in Labor Education Viewpoints, Fall 1961.
  - White House Conference on Narcotics and Drug Abuse, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    September 1952.
  - Workmen's Circle, 1959-1963 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    Incl. Tyler article "Decline of the Big City Machines", January 1962, Tyler speech on occasion of Workmen's Circle's Diamond Jubilees 1959.
  - Young American Creates, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    Incl. Corres. re design competition.
  - Youth Committee Against Poverty, 1966-1967 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Series VII. Instructional material., 1950-1961
  - General Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1957 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1957 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1959 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1959 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Courses. Undated. Class evaluations. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Courses. Undated. Statistical tables. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Courses. Undated. ILGWU History (Box 63, Folder 10)
    Incl. bibliography, reading assignments.
  - Courses. Undated. Outline for course on Local Union Administration. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Evening Training Institutes [folder 1 of 2], 1957-1960 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Evening Training Institutes [folder 2 of 2], 1957-1960 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Financial Matters, 1953-1959 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Incl. bills, copies of advertisements.
  - Financial Matters, 1956-1958 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Records of Training Institute expenses, such as instructors' fees, student expenses, staff expenses.
  - Indonesian Students, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Indonesian Students, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Indonesian Students, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Incl. Corres. re itinerary.
  - Indonesian Students [folder 1 of 2], 1957 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Indonesian Students [folder 2 of 2], 1957 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Indonesian Students, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Indonesian Students [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Indonesian Students [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Instructors, Silberman, Charles, 1950-1952 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Instructors, Stein, Leon, 1950-1958 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Instructors, Taft, Philip [folder 1 of 2], 1950-1957 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    Incl. outline of plan for study of the American Federation of Labor.
  - Instructors, Taft, Philip [folder 2 of 2], 1950-1957 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Instructors, Strumthal, Adolf [folder 1 of 2], 1950-1958 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Instructors, Strumthal, Adolf [folder 2 of 2], 1950-1958 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Instructors, Toyer, Aurelia, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Instructors, Vladeck, Steve, 1951-1953 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Instructors, Warner, Betty, 1951-1952 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Instructors, Weiss, Abraham, 1950-1957 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Instructors, Weisz, Morris, 1950-1952 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous. Undated. Outline and part of speech The Politics of Protest. (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Price Lists for Garments, 1947-1953 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Recruitment of Students for ILGWU Training Institute on College Campuses [folder 1 of 4], 1957 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Recruitment of Students for ILGWU Training Institute on College Campuses [folder 2 of 4], 1957 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Recruitment of Students for ILGWU Training Institute on College Campuses [folder 3 of 4], 1957 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Recruitment of Students for ILGWU Training Institute on College Campuses [folder 4 of 4], 1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Recruitment of Students for ILGWU Training Institute on College Campuses, 1958 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Recruitment of Students for ILGWU Training Institute on College Campuses, 1959 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Recruitment of Students for ILGWU Training Institute, 1957-1958 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Student Reports [folder 1 of 6], 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    Weekly reports by students on their field work activities.
  - Student Reports [folder 2 of 6], 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Student Reports [folder 3 of 6], 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Student Reports [folder 4 of 6], 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Student Reports [folder 5 of 6], 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Student Reports [folder 6 of 6], 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 13)